[Music]
[âm nhạc]
[Applause]
[Vỗ tay]
Spring arrives, countless flowers bloom, spring
mùa xuân đến muôn hoa đua nở mùa xuân
arrives, I go to the temple, I pray to the
đến con đi lễ chùa vào chùa vái phật
sacred Buddha,
linh thiêng
spring arrives, singing and dancing, celebrating the arrival of spring,
mùa xuân đến hát ca xeo Mừng mùa xuân
so much joy and excitement. The fragrant incense
đến bao vui rộn ràng Hương tâm ngạt
welcomes spring, in
hương đón xuân về
the evening I offer prayers to Buddha Shakyamuni, praying
tối đau tôi lại đưa Phật Thích Ca
for my family's health,
Cầu cho gia đình mạnh khỏe
praying for my children and grandchildren to have a hundred flowers, and
cầu cho con cháu trăm hoa
good wishes for every home,
câu chúc luôn may mắn đến với mọi nhà
praying for peace in the country, joy in every home, a
cầu cho đất nước bình an nhà nhà an vui
season of victory, a warm and peaceful spring, pure and
mùa mang thắng lợi mùa xuân ấm êm thuần
beautiful, hoping for a year full of love. In
hoa mong một năm ngập tràn yêu thương
spring I go to the temple
mùa xuân con đến chùa
[Music] to
[âm nhạc]
help people, following the Buddha's teachings, very
giúp đỡ mọi người theo lời Phật rất
diligent in practicing, doing much,
con người chăm chỉ tu hành làm nhiều
knowing kindness, living a life of deep love.
biết Hiền sống đời tình thắm
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
[Applause]
[Vỗ tay]
Spring arrives, countless flowers bloom, spring arrives, I
mùa xuân đến muôn hoa đua nở mùa xuân
go to the temple, I pray to the
đến con đi lễ chùa vào chùa với phật
sacred Buddha,
linh thiêng
spring arrives, singing and dancing, celebrating the arrival of spring, the fragrant incense welcomes spring, in the
mùa xuân đến hát ca xeo Mừng mùa xuân
evening I bow to the Buddha Shakyamuni, praying for my
cuối đâu Con lạy Đức Phật Thích Ca
family's health, praying for my children to have
Cầu cho gia đình mạnh khỏe
a hundred flowers, and
cầu cho con trao trăm hoa
good wishes for every home,
câu chúc luôn may mắn đến với mọi nhà
praying for peace in the country, joy in every home, a season of
cầu cho đất nước bình an nhà nhà an vui
victory, a warm and peaceful spring, pure and beautiful.
Muộn Màng thắng lợi mùa xuân ấm êm thuần
Buddha Shakyamuni.
Đức Phật Thích Ca
People live a peaceful life, helping
Con người sống đời yên tiền giúp đỡ mọi
others according to Buddha's teachings,
người theo lời Phật dạy
doing many good deeds. Living a virtuous life. Love. Poetry
làm nhiều việc Hiền sống đời Tình Thơ
[music]
[âm nhạc]